CHICAGO MOONSHINE is an Art Deco serif All Caps display font.

Please note that this is primarily for headlines, logos posters in large size.

This is the demo version and is free for testing purposes and personal use. For full version and / or commercial  license please visit 

store.rolandhuse.com

The full version character set contains Western and Eastern European latin languages, basic symbols and punctuation. The Capital letters has geometric patterns and in place of lowercase letters there are filled in Capitals.

Inquiries, feedback, customisation requests and/or extra characters please contact me here or via rolandhuse.com

* * *

Background image (taken from Unsplash) credits:

Chicago at night : Prafulla Chandra https://unsplash.com/@prafulla90

Moon I photoshopped onto the night skyline: Jason Darrell https://unsplash.com/@zebedeerox

* * *

You may not

sell these fonts or claim them as your own.

edit or rename these fonts.

redistribute these fonts.

Find more of my works on instagram @rolandhusedesign

Thank you and hope you like this font!

Have a great day and good luck with your work,

Roland